A Guide to the Papers of the Virginia Quarterly Review, 1925-1935
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Sparrow, Carroll 1928-1935, 41 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Spencer, Henry R. 1927, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Spencer, Lilian White 1927-1931, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Spender, Stephen 1935 September 23, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Spencer (Box 41)
- Spykman, Nicholas 1934, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Squier, John 1925 March 27, 2 pp. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Squire, John Collings 1924-1928, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Squire, Mary 1927, 4 items. Letters, Virginia Quarterly Review to Squire (Box 42)
- Stafford, Lawrence 1931-1935, 28 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Stallings, Laurence 1930-1932, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Stanard, Mary Newton 1925-1926, 5 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Starkie, Walter 1929-1930, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Starrett, Vincent 1925-1932, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Stead, William Force 1927-1935, 55 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Stearns, Florence Dickinson 1932-1933, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Steffens, Lincoln 1932 September 29, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Steffens (Box 42)
- Stephenson, Nathaniel 1925-1927, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Sterling, George 1925, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Stevens, Mary Woodhall 1926-1930, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Stevenson, Lionel 1929-1933, 18 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Stewart, Annarrah Lee 1935, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Stewart, Douglas H. 1934, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Still, James 1934-1935, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Stillman, Mildred Whitney 1927-1928, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Frederick A. Stokes Co. 1928-1933, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Stolberg-Wernigerode, Otto zu 1929, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Stone, Edward 1925-1926, 3 items. Letters with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Stone, William T. 1934, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Stoney, Samuel Gaillard 1932-1934, 23 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Stork, Charles Wharton 1926-1935, 25 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Stribling, Thomas Sigismund 1929-1930, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Strong, Leonard Alfred 1928-1934, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Stuart, Jesse 1932-1935, 38 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Sullivan, Mark 1925-1932, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Swanson, Claude 1931 December 30, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Swem, Earl Gregg 1925, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Szepesi, Eugene 1927-1929, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Miscellaneous Sa-Sn 1925-1935, ca. 1000 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 42)
- Miscellaneous So-Sy (Box 43)
- Taft, William Howard 1925 January 16, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Taggard, Genevieve 1933, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Tarbell, Ida 1925, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Tate, Caroline Gordoń 1932, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Tate, Allen 1925-1935, ca. 85 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Tatum, Edith 1925-1928, 23 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Tawney, R. H. 1933, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Taylor, Harold Spencer 1929-1933, 23 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Tazewell, Littleton Waller 1926, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Teasdale, Sara 1925 May 15, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Templin, Ernest 1933-1934, 15 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Thomas, Norman 1930-1934, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Thomas, Rosemary ca. 1925, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Towne, Charles Hanson 1935 December 4, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Towne (Box 44)
- Thomapson, Holland 1929, 2 items. Letters to Thompson (Box 44)
- Thompson, James Westfall 1928-1931, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Thompson, James M. 1925 March 24, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Thorndike, Ashley 1925 January 19, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Thwing, Charles 1925, 4 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Ticknor, Caroline 1932, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Tigert, John 1929, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Tinker, Edward Larocque 1932-1933, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Tooker, L. Frank 1925, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Tracy, Henry 1931, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Trigg, Emma Gray 1926-1933, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Troubetzkoy, Amélie Rives 1925-1935, 51 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Trowbridge, Augustus 1930 May 10, 2 l. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Tucker, Beverley 1926-1935, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Tucker, Robert 1925, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Turlington, Edgar 1927, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Turner, Nancy Byrd 1925-1932, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Turner, Raymond 1925-1929, 31 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Miscellaneous Ta-Tn 1925-1935, ca. 500 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 44)
- Miscellaneous To-Ty (Box 45)
- Underwood, Oscar 1925-1927, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 45)
- University of Chicago Press 1925-1935, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 45)
- Untermeyer, Jean Starr 1931 June 26, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 45)
- Untermeyer, Louis 1926-1931, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 45)
- Uzzell, Thomas 1933-1935, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 45)
- Miscellaneous U 1925-1934, 21 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 45)
- Van Doren, Carl 1929, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 45)
- Van Doren, Dorothy 1931-1932, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 45)
- Van Doren, Irita 1926-1935, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 45)
- Van Doren, Mark 1930-1933, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 45)
- Van Paassen, Pierre 1932-1933, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 45)
- Viking Press 1930-1935, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 45)
- Vinal, Harold 1927-1931, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 45)
- Vose, Caroline 1925-1931, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 45)
- Miscellaneous V 1925-1935, ca. 100 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 45)
- Wade, John Donald 1929-1935, 53 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wagenknecht, Edward 1925-1934, ca. 175 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wagner, Robert 1935 July 12, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Walker, Robert Sparks 1926-1935, 26 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Walker, William 1929-1930, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wallace, Henry Agard 1927, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Waring, T.R. 1931-1934, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Warren, Austin 1928-1930, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Warren, Robert Penn 1930-1935, 59 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Warrin, Frank L. 1932, 18 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Waugh, Evelyn 1933 December 12, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Waugh (Box 46)
- Weart, Edith 1929-1932, 20 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wecter, Dixon 1934-1935, 31 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Weddell, Alexander 1928-1931, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Weekley, Ernest 1934, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wegg, Tabbot 1934, 20 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wehle, Harry B. 1931, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Weismiller, Edward 1935, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Welles, Winifred 1933, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wells, Herbert George, Secretary of 1933, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wertenbaker, G. Peyton 1925-1932, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- West, Geoffrey 1931-1932, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Whallon, Archer 1927, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wharton, Edith 1927 September 19, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Wharton (Box 46)
- Wharton, James B. 1927-1934, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wheeler, William Morton 1930 September 17, 2 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Wheeler (Box 46)
- Wheelock, John Hall 1925-1926, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wheelwright, John 1932 February 17, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Wheelwright (Box 46)
- Wheelwright, Philip 1932-1933, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Whipple, Leon 1925, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- White, Newman Ivey 1929, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- White, Richard 1925-1932, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- White, William Allen 1925, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Whitehead, Alfred North 1931 September 29, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Whitehead (Box 46)
- Whiteley, Emily Stone 1928-1935, 51 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wilcox, Uthai Vincent 1925-1935, 20 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Williams, Blanche Colton 1929, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Williams, Stanley T. 1925-1933, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wilson, Charles Morrow 1930-1934, 41 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wilson, Edmund 1930-1935, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wilson, James Southall 1928-1935, ca. 125 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wingfield-Stratford, Esmé 1934 April 19, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Wingfield-Stratford (Box 46)
- Winston, Robert 1929-1933, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Winters, Yvor 1930-1934, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wolfe, Bertram D. 1930-1934, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wolfe, Thomas 1932-1934, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Woodruff, M. Dorothy 1928-1935, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Woolf, Virginia 1934, 2 items. Letters, Virginia Quarterly Review to Woolf (Box 46)
- Wranek, William 1926-1935, 2 items. Letters, Virginia Quarterly Review to Wranek (Box 46)
- Wright, David McCord 1934, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wright, R. Charlton 1930-1933, 39 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wriston, Henry 1925-1928, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 46)
- Wyatt, Edith Franklin 1925-1933, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 47)
- Wyllie, John Cook 1928-1935, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 47)
- Wynn, Dudley 1935, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 47)
- Miscellaneous W 1925-1935, ca. 650 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 47)
- Yale University Press 1928-1934, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 47)
- Yeats, William Butler 1935 September 23, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Yeats (Box 47)
- Young, Stark 1925-1935, ca. 100 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 47)
- Zehmer, George 1925-1931, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 47)
- Miscellaneous X-Y-Z 1925-1935, ca. 75 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 47)